<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lucas Sartore</title>
    <link>https://lysrt.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lucas Sartore</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 12:27:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lysrt.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a SVG Parser in Go</title>
      <link>https://lysrt.net/post/build-svg-parser-1-lexer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 12:27:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lysrt.net/post/build-svg-parser-1-lexer/</guid>
      <description>This post is part of a series on writing a SVG parser in Go. It is inspired by the amazing book from Thorsten Ball (https://interpreterbook.com/).
 As developers, we use parsers everyday: from web browser engines, to compilers, interpreters and linters.
But when it comes to write one yourself, to read a custom config file, or protocol, where would you start?
Most of the time the easiest way is to generate the code of the parser using a generator, like yacc or ANTLR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Caddy on Linux with systemd</title>
      <link>https://lysrt.net/post/using-caddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 10:58:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lysrt.net/post/using-caddy/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard about Caddy. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t, you should definitely check it out.
Caddy is an amazing web server, with automatic HTTPS. It uses HTTP/2 by default, and is so simple to configure.
If you host your own website on a dedicated server, at some point you had to decide which web server to use. Generally it will be Apache HTTP Server or NGINX.
They do the work, sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lysrt.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lysrt.net/about/</guid>
      <description> About me Spare time gopher. I studied in Grenoble INP - Esisar.
Go, C#, Java, Python.
Projects Android apps  Simple Wallet ColorMix Unicolor  Cryptocurrencies  Market places API connectivity Coins price monitoring  Headless web rendering engine  Bro (inspired by Robinson)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>